Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 1 and District 1 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE National Office Records Relating to District 1 and District 1 Locals
1936-1994
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
UE.4.1.1
12.5 Linear Feet (10 boxes)
This series contains files on United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) District 1 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts.
Scope and Content Notes
District 1 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) included locals in eastern Pennsylvania, southern New Jersey, Delaware, Maryland and Virginia. These locals are now part of the UE's Eastern Region. This series contains files on UE District 1 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts. Most of the correspondence is between UE national officers and district or local officers.
Arrangement
This series has been arranged into two subseries. The first contains records pertaining to District 1. The other subseries contains records pertaining to specific locals within the district, and are further arranged numerically by local number into sections.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America in 1975, 1986, 1997, and 2001.
Previous Citation
UE National Office Records Relating to District 1 and District 1 Locals, 1936-1994, UE.4.1.1, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Related Material
UE District 1 Records, 1950s-1986, UE.15.1, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 107 Records, 1933-1987, UE.16.107, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 124 Records, 1980s-1990s, UE.16.124, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Labor unions -- New Jersey -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- Pennyslvania -- History -- 20th century; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- History; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- New Jersey -- History; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- History; Correspondence; Labor unions -- Organizing -- United States -- History; Labor; Labor unions -- United States -- History; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 1; Emspak, Julius; Matles, James J.; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
- District 1, 1.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This subseries contains files maintained by the UE National Office pertaining to District 1. Included is correspondence from District Presidents Albert Newcomb, Harry Block, James Price, Ernest Moyer, Peter Besch, Robert Kyler, Richard Williams, Thomas Sharkey and Nicholas Onofaro, in addition to general district correspondence. Also present are district executive council and staff meeting minutes. These records include information on district staffing, finances and political action, as well as local strikes and raids by other unions.
  - District 1 Constitution and By-Laws, 1943-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Constitution District 1 Council with David Davis Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, October 8, 1943; 1.
    - Proposed Changes to Constitution of District 1 Council, UERMWA-CIO, January 1948; 2.
    - Amendment to the Constitution, District 1 Council, 3.
  - District 1 President Harry Block Memorandum to All Locals in UE District #1 and UE National Office Regarding Veteran's Pay, January 14, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - District 1 President James Price Correspondence, 1946-1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - James Price to All Philadelphia CIO Unions and UE District Presidents Regarding Trial of District 1 Pickets, November 25, 1946; 1.
    - Price to All Staff Members, John Welsh, David Neish, and James Matles Regarding Staff Expenses, December 2, 1946; 2.
    - Price to District 1 Locals, Officers, Executive Board, and Shop Stewards Regarding 1947 Negotiations, February 20, 1947; 3.
    - Price to District 1 Locals, Organizers, and UE District Presidents Regarding Trial of UE Pickets, February 20, 1947; 4.
    - Price to All UE Locals, UE District Presidents, and Philadelphia CIO Locals Regarding Trial of UE Pickets, March 3, 1947; 5.
    - Price to District 1 Locals, UE District Presidents, and Philadelphia CIO Unions Regarding Trial of UE Pickets, April 2, 1947; 6.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding Van Gelder Appointment with Note from Price to Matles, May 12, 1947; 7.
    - Price to All UE Locals, Executive Officers and District Council Delegates Regarding District Council Meeting, December 23, 1947; 8.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding the Taft-Hartley Law, 1947; 9.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding Internal Revenue Service, April 26, 1948; 10.
    - Price to Secretaries of District 1 Locals Regarding Educational Conference, February 23, 1948; 11.
    - Price to Secretaries of District 1 Locals Regarding Arthur Gaeth Broadcasts with Arthur Gaeth Poster, February 18, 1948; 12.
    - Price to District 1 Locals, International Representatives, and Field Organizers Regarding Educational Conferences, March, 1948; 13.
    - Price to District 1 Locals, International Representatives, and Field Organizers Regarding Electric Service Manufacturing Strike, March 9, 1948; 14.
    - Price to District 1 Philadelphia Locals Regarding Recreational Activities, March 9, 1948; 15.
    - Price Memo, "Urgent!!", Regarding Office Supplies, February 23, 1948; 16.
    - Price to All UE Locals Regarding Electric Service Manufacturing Strike, March 25, 1948; 17.
    - Price to Secretaries of District 1 Locals Regarding Educational Conference, March 25, 1948; 18.
    - Price to Secretaries of District 1 Locals Regarding the Film "The Great Swindle" with Response Postcard, March 25, 1948; 19.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding UAW Raiding with Letter from Julius Emspak to Phillip Murray Dated March 16, 1948, Regarding UAW Raiding, March 22, 1948; 20.
    - Price to UAW-CIO Locals in Pennsylvania Regarding UAW Raiding, March 23, 1948; 21.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding Wage Negotiations, April 13, 1948; 22.
    - Price to District 1 Locals and Field Organizers Regarding Arthur Gaeth Broadcasts with an Arthur Gaeth Broadcast Leaflet, April 13, 1948; 23.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding Local 150 Strike, May 11, 1948; 24.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding the Film "The Great Swindle", May 11, 1948; 25.
    - Price to Emspak Regarding Shotte and Koeuting Strikes, August 5, 1948; 26.
    - Price to All UE Districts Regarding Local 136 Strike, August 24, 1948; 27.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding Local 135 Strike, August 24, 1948; 28.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding Local 136 Strike, August 27, 1948; 29.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding the Strike and Defense Fund, October 14, 1948; 30.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding the Pamphlet We Fought for Our Union, October 14, 1948; 31.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding Stewards Conference with the Leaflet "Shop Stewards Conference", December 21, 1948; 32.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding United Office and Professional Workers of America Prudential Election, March 14, 1949; 33.
    - Price to District 1 Locals in Pennsylvania Regarding Political Action with List of Members of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives, March 16, 1949; 34.
    - Price to Philadelphia Area UE Locals Regarding Wage Campaign with Report on the May 13, 1948 District 1 Wage Campaign Meeting of Philadelphia Locals, May 14, 1948; 35.
    - Price to District 1 Locals and UE District Offices Regarding Miscellaneous District Matters, May 25, 1949; 36.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding an Unemployment Meeting at Local 107, May 25, 1949; 37.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding Local 107, April 21, 1949; 38.
    - Price to District 1 Locals and UE District Offices Regarding Frank Hellman Case, May 25, 1949; 39.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding the USW Strike of American Chain & Cable Company Workers in Pittston, Pennsylvania, March 3, 1950; 40.
    - Price Press Release to UE News Regarding Wage Control Demonstration, December 1951; 41.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding National Women's Conference, February 17, 1953; 42.
    - Price to District 1 Locals Regarding Local 1113 Strike, February 23, 1953; 43.
    - Price Memo Regarding Metal Workers Conference, February 26, 1953; 44.
    - Price to District 1 Locals and District Executive Board Members Regarding Fighting Fund, March 13, 1952; 45.
    - News Clipping from the Philadephia Bulletin Regarding Price Resignation, August 7, 1953; 46.
  - District 1 President Ernest Moyer Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Ernest Moyer Notice to District 1 Locals Regarding James Price Resignation, August 1953; 1.
    - Moyer Letter Regarding District 1 Convention, November 23, 1953; 2.
    - Moyer to District 1 Locals Regarding Local 107 Representation Election, January 15, 1954; 3.
  - District 1 President Peter Besch Correspondence, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Peter Besch Notice Regarding District Office, February 1955; 1.
    - Besch to District 1 Locals and Staff Members Regarding the Brownell-Butler Act Case against the Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers Union (MMSW) with a UE Local 155 Shop Stewards Council Resolution Dated August 2, 1955, Regarding MMSW, August 1955; 2.
    - Besch to Senators and Congressmen in District 1 Area Regarding Brownell and MMSW, August, 1955; 3.
    - Besch to Other Unions Regarding MMSW, August 1955; 4.
    - Besch to District 1 Locals Regarding the Third District 1 Convention with an October 4, 1955, Letter from Max Helfand to UE District 1 Locals Regarding the District 1 Banquet, a District 1 Convention Leaflet and Credentials Form, 5.
  - District 1 President Peter Besch Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - District 1 President Robert Kyler Correspondence, 1958-1962, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - District 1 President Richard Williams Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - District 1 President Thomas F. Sharkey Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - District 1 President Nicholas Onofaro Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - District 1 Treasurer Lewis Cohen Reports, October 1936-February 1937 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - District 1 Secretary Samuel Basmajian Correspondence Regarding District Council Meeting with Envelope, March 26, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - International Representative Carl Bersing Reports, 1941-1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Report Regarding Bendix Organizing Campaign with Carl Bersing Letter to James Matles Regarding the Report, January 13, 1943; 1.
    - Statement on the Present Status of Staff and a Proposed Plan of Assignments Affecting the Activities of the District 1 Office in Philadelphia Concerning Staff Members and Organization with a Letter from Bersing to Albert Fitzgerald and Julius Emspak Regarding the Report and a Staff Reporting Form, April 13, 1941; 2.
    - Organizational Activity Carried on in District 1 by International Staff Members, May 3, 1944; 3.
  - International Representative Peter Besch Reports, 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - District 1 UE Organizational Status with Peter Besch Letter to Julius Emspak Regarding the Report, June 11, 1945; 1.
    - Monthly Organizer's Report, November 30, 1943; 2.
    - Monthly Organizer's Report with May 1, 1944, Besch Letter to Emspak Regarding the Report, April 1944; 3.
    - International Representatives Report, June 1944; 4.
    - Organization Report, October 29, 1945; 5.
  - District 1 Executive Council Minutes, May 1936-March 1937, December 1940 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - District 1 Executive Council Minutes, 1942-1943, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Minutes with Supplemental Material, June 4, 1942; 1.
    - Minutes, August 6, 1942; 2.
    - Minutes with Harry Block Letter, February 11, 1943; 3.
    - Minutes, December 5, 1946; 4.
    - Minutes with Report by James Price, January 9, 1947; 5.
    - Minutes, February 6, 1947; 6.
    - Minutes with Thomas F. Delaney Letter to Tom Wright Dating March 17, 1947, Regarding the Minutes, March 6, 1947; 7.
    - Minutes with President's Report, April 10, 1947; 8.
    - Minutes with President's Report and April 10, 1947, Report of Paul Boylan, May 1, 1947; 9.
    - Minutes with District President Price's Report, International President Fitzgerald's Report, and Paul Boylan's Report for May, June 5, 1947; 10.
    - Minutes, July 10, 1947; 11.
    - Minutes with Report and Recommendations of District PAC Committee, August 7, 1947; 12.
    - Minutes, October 9, 1947; 13.
    - Minutes, November 6, 1947; 14.
  - District 1 Executive Council Minutes, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - District 1 Council and District Executive Board Minutes, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - District 1 Council and District Executive Board Minutes, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - District 1 Council and District Executive Board Minutes, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - District 1 Council and District Executive Board Minutes, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - District 1 Council and District Executive Board Minutes, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - District 1 Council and District Executive Board Minutes, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
  - District 1 Council Minutes, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - District 1 Council and District Executive Board Minutes, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - District 1 Council and District Executive Board Minutes, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - District 1 Council and District Executive Board Minutes, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - District 1 Council and District Executive Board Minutes, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - District 1 Council and District Executive Board Minutes, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - District 1 Council and District Executive Board Minutes, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - District 1 Council Minutes, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - District 1 Executive Council Minutes, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, January 8, 1948; 1.
    - Minutes with UE District 1 Organizer's Report, February 5, 1948; 2.
    - Minutes with UE District 1 Organizer's Report, March 4, 1948; 3.
    - Minutes with UE District 1 Organizer's Report, April 1, 1948; 4.
    - Minutes with Report of International Representative Rhine, May 6, 1948; 5.
    - Minutes with Report of District Organizer Ruzansky, June 10, 1948; 6.
    - Minutes, August 12, 1948; 7.
    - Minutes with Report of District Organizer Ruzansky, July 1, 1948; 8.
    - Minutes with Statement by Albert J. Fitzgerald, September 2, 1948; 9.
    - Minutes with Resolution Regarding West Coast Maritime Unions Strike, October 7, 1948; 10.
    - Minutes with Reports of District Organizer Ruzansky and a Resolution Regarding the Taft-Hartley Law, November 4, 1948; 11.
    - Minutes with Report of District Organizer Ruzansky, December 2, 1948; 12.
  - District 1 Executive Council Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Minutes with Report of District Organizer Ruzansky, January 6, 1949; 1.
    - Minutes with Report of District Organizer Ruzansky, February 3, 1949; 2.
    - Minutes with Report of District Organizer Ruzansky, March 3, 1949; 3.
    - Minutes with District Organizer's Report, May 5, 1949; 4.
    - Minutes with Report of Organizer Ruzansky, June 2, 1949; 5.
    - Minutes with District Organizer's Report and Thomas Delaney Letter to all UE District 1 Council Delegates, July 7, 1949; 6.
    - Minutes with Report of District Organizer Ruzansky, August 4, 1949; 7.
    - Minutes with Report of District Organizer Ruzansky, September 8, 1949; 8.
    - Minutes with District Organizer's Report, October 6, 1949; 9.
    - Minutes, January 5, 1950; 10.
    - Minutes, February 2, 1950; 11.
    - Minutes, March 2, 1950; 12.
    - Minutes, September 7, 1950; 13.
  - District 1 Executive Council Minutes, 1948-1953 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - District 1 Executive Council Minutes, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - District 1 Council Meeting Minutes, 1959-1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - District 1 Executive Council Minutes, 1980-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - District 1 Council Correspondence, 1957-1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - District 1 Constitutional Convention Minutes and Officer's Reports, 1956-1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - District 1 Constitutional Convention Minutes and Officer's Reports, 1964-1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - District 1 Constitutional Convention Correspondence, 1957-1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - District 1 Executive Council Literature, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Election of CIO Council Officers Regarding Vote Totals, January 13, 1935; 1.
    - Sample Ballot for Election of CIO Council Officers for 1938, January 13, 1938; 2.
    - Relief and Welfare Committee Letter to Philadelphia Industrial Union Council Executive Board Regarding the Works Projects Administration, January 21, 1938; 3.
    - Secretaries of Locals in District 1, 1935-1940; 4.
    - List of District 1 Local Secretaries with L. Geiselman Letter to Julius Emspak Dating October 26, 1942, Regarding the Address List, October 1942; 5.
    - Application for a Local Union Charter, November 16, 1944; 6.
    - Disposition of Staff, October 1, 1945; 7.
    - Shops within UE Jurisdiction in Lancaster, Pennsylvania, with Memo to Peter Besch Regarding the Chart, November 3, 1945; 8.
    - National Staff Members Currently Engaged in District 1 with Their Assignments and a List of Shops Won in District 1 Since March 1, May 16, 1946; 9.
    - Curtis D. Heffner Weekly Report, September 21, 1946; 10.
    - Meeting of CIO on the Newspaper Strike, December 5, 1946; 11.
    - Organization Chart, 1943-1946; 12.
    - Plan of Action, Baltimore, 1943-1946; 13.
    - District 1, Radio Broadcast Script, June 27, 1947; 14.
    - UE District 1 Wage Gains, July 7, 1948; 15.
    - District 1 Council Election Results, October 6, 1949; 16.
    - Proposed Community Campaign in Support of CIO Wage Program, 1946-1949; 17.
    - Statement of Policy for the 15th Annual UE Convention, August 31, 1950; 18.
    - Wage Negotiations Memo, April 11, 1952; 19.
    - Memo on IUE Settlement of Philco Strike, June 1954; 20.
  - District 1 Miscellaneous Literature, C.W. Fowler Request for Vacation, May 18, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - District 1 Executive Council Resolutions, 1938, 1941-1948 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Wage Cuts, January 13, 1938; 1.
    - Horse Hair Industry, January 13, 1938; 2.
    - Taxation, January 13, 1938; 3.
    - Shoe Strike, January 13, 1938; 4.
    - National Leather Workers Association Strike, January 13, 1938; 5.
    - General Foods Boycott, January 13, 1938; 6.
    - Radio Broadcasts, January 13, 1938; 7.
    - Defense Strike Bill, April 1941; 8.
    - Second Front with Samuel Basmajian Letter to Julius Emspak Regarding Resolution, March 24, 1943; 9.
    - Nazi Atrocities, 1943; 10.
    - Resistance Movements, December 1944; 11.
    - War Manpower Commission with Henry Block Letter to UE Regarding Resolution, July 1944; 12.
    - Crimean Conference with March 9, 1945, Basmajian Letter to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding the Resolution, March 1, 1945; 13.
    - World Trade Union Conference, March 1, 1945; 14.
    - Local 133 and International Representative with Thomas Delaney Letter to Fitzgerald, May 9, 1946; 15.
    - United Mine Workers of America Strike, December 5, 1946; 16.
    - School Aid, December 5, 1946; 17.
    - UMWA Strike, December 5, 1946; 18.
    - Rent Control, January 9, 1947; 19.
    - Greek Anti-Strike Law, February 5, 1948; 20.
    - Philadelphia Transit Company Fare Increase, March 4, 1948; 21.
  - District 1 Executive Council Resolutions, 1948-1950 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Victor Riesel, March 4, 1948; 1.
    - Frank Hellman Deportation, March 4, 1948; 2.
    - United Auto Workers Raiding with April 16, 1948, Thomas Delaney Letter to Julius Emspak Regarding Resolution, April 1, 1948; 3.
    - Mundt-Nixon Bill with May 7, 1948, James Price Letter to All Locals Regarding Resolution, May 6, 1948; 4.
    - Security Clearances, August 12, 1948; 5.
    - James Kutchev Case with a Copy of the Taft-Hartley Law, November 4, 1948; 6.
    - Condemnation of Harry Block's Local 124 Activity, November 4, 1948; 7.
    - Pennsylvania Unemployment Compensation Law, December 2, 1948; 8.
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and the Taft-Hartley Act, January 6, 1949; 9.
    - ILGWU and the Taft Hartley Law with January 11, 1949, Delaney Letter to Emspak Regarding Resolution, January 10, 1949; 10.
    - Wiretapping, February 3, 1949; 11.
    - Public Schools, February 3, 1949; 12.
    - Ober Bill, March 3, 1949; 13.
    - Rice and Holman Strikes, May 5, 1949; 14.
    - Unemployment and Special Session, Pennsylvania Legislative, July 7, 1949; 15.
    - East German Railroad Strikes, July 7, 1949; 16.
    - Strikebreaking with July 13, 1949, Delaney Letter to Emspak Regarding Resolutions, July 7, 1949; 17.
    - Unemployment and Special Session, PA Legislature with July 18, 1949, Delaney Letter to UE District 1 Council Delegates Regarding Correction Resolutions, July 7, 1949; 18.
    - Peekskills Riot with Letter Regarding United Steelworkers Raiding, September 8, 1949; 19.
    - United Mine Workers of America Strike, February 2, 1950; 20.
    - Crowe Bill, 21.
  - District 1 Executive Council Resolution Concerning Local 813, Bucyrus-Erie Strike with Price Letter to District 1 Locals Regarding Resolution, September 27, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - District 1 Political Action Committee, 1945-1947 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Harry Block Letter to Julius Emspak Regarding PAC Checks, August 1, 1945; 1.
    - Block Letter to Emspak Regarding PAC Checks, August 8, 1945; 2.
    - Emspak Letter to Block Regarding PAC Receipts, August 17, 1945; 3.
    - John Welsh Letter to UE Regarding PAC Check, September 4, 1945; 4.
    - Emspak Letter to Welsh Regarding PAC Receipts, September 11, 1945; 5.
    - Emspak Letter to Welsh Regarding PAC Receipts, October 22, 1945; 6.
    - Block Letter to UE Regarding Membership Lests, May 10, 1946; 7.
    - George Yaunches Letter to Emspak Regarding PAC Funds, July-August 1946; 8.
    - Joseph Kelly Letter to UE Regarding 1946 Elections, October 1946; 9.
    - Emspak Telegram to Block, Peter Besch, and Francis White Regarding 1946 Elections with Emspak Letter to Kelly Regarding Telegram, October 22, 1946; 10.
    - PAC Dollar Drive Status with James Price Letter to Emspak Dated October 31, 1947, Regarding PAC Report, 11.
  - District 1 Political Action Committee, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Outline of UE Legislative-Political Action, January 4-5, 1954; 1.
    - C.W. Fowler Letter to District 1 Locals, January 27, 1954; 2.
  - District 1 Political Action, 1966-1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - District 1 Staff Meetings Minutes, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Minutes, April 28, 1944; 1.
    - Minutes, May 22, 1944; 2.
    - Minutes, June 8, 1944; 3.
    - Minutes with Carl Bersing Letter to All Business Representatives and Organizers Dated June 30, 1944, Regarding Staff Meetings, June 23, 1944; 4.
    - Minutes with Peter Besch Letter to All Business Representatives and Organizers Dated July 11, 1944, Regarding Minutes, July 7, 1944; 5.
    - Minutes, July 25, 1944; 6.
    - Minutes, August 25, 1944; 7.
  - District 1 Staff Meetings Minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - District 1 Staff Meeting Minutes, Baltimore, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Minutes, July 27, 1944; 1.
    - Minutes with Peter Besch Letter to Julius Emspak Dated October 3, 1944, Regarding Minutes, September 20, 1944; 2.
    - Minutes, March 15, 1942; 3.
    - Minutes, March 29, 1945; 4.